Guide to the Robert Wasserman papers, 1956-2001.
Robert Wasserman papers, 1956-2001
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert Wasserman papers, 1956-2001.
21-40-3519
R.H.(Robert Harold), Wasserman 1926-
2.4 cubic ft.
{comma separted list of material formats; end with period.}
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, biographical information, and course material.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of biomedical sciences in the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, biographical information, and course material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wasserman, R.H.1926-; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Faculty.
Subjects:
Veterinary Medicine--Study and teaching.; Veterinary Medicine--Research.; Biology--Research.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of donor until 2016
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence - Department, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20-23)
- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - Department, January - July 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Correspondence - Department, August- December 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondence - Department, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
- Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Correspondence- Department, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence- Stanniocalcin Project, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
- Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
- Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
- Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
- Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Dept. of Physiology Meeting Minutes, 1983- May 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Dept. of Physiology Meeting Minutes, July 1984 - June 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Section of Physiology Meeting Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Section of Physiology Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Department of Physiology Review, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Course Material, Spring 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2-4)
- Course Material - Minerals Course, Spring 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
- Photographs of the Transfer of Calcium and Strontium Across Biological Membranes Conference, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Articles by Wasserman, 1956-1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Awards, 1968-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)